productreview.com.au 2015-12-28

# Privacy Policy - ProductReview.com.au

20 May 2014

##### Protecting your privacy

ProductReview.com.au Pty Limited ("ProductReview", "we", "our", "us") is committed to protecting your privacy. We are bound by the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (“Privacy Act”), which sets out a number of principles concerning the protection of your personal information known as the Australian Privacy Principles. 

This privacy statement sets out the type of information we collect, how we use it and who we may share it with. It may be amended from time to time and a current version is available on this page. 

##### What personal information do we collect?

We collect personal information submitted to ProductReview such as:

  * name;
  * email address;
  * mailing or street address;
  * telephone number;
  * gender;
  * birth date;
  * invoices and product receipts;
  * email communications;
  * bank statements

##### What non-personal information do we collect?

We collect non-personal statistical information on visitors such as:

  * IP address;
  * visit date and time;
  * visit duration;
  * referring site;
  * type of web browser;
  * pages accessed on ProductReview;
  * other information provided by browser's HTTP headers

##### Using personal information

The primary purpose for which we collect information about you is to enable us to perform our business activities and functions and to provide best possible quality of customer service. We collect, hold and use your personal information for the following purposes: 

  * to verify your identity;
  * to provide products and services to you;
  * to provide you with news, information or advice about our existing and new products and services;
  * to communicate with you including by email or phone;
  * to manage and enhance our products and services;
  * to personalise and customise your experience;
  * to provide you with access to protected areas of ProductReview;
  * to conduct business processing functions for operation of ProductReview;
  * to investigate any complaints about or made by you, or if we have reason to suspect that you are in breach of any of our terms and conditions or that you are or have been otherwise engaged in any unlawful activity

##### Registration

If you wish to submit a review, comment, question, or report certain content you must register on ProductReview to create a user account. All information you provide when registering user account including your name, address, email address, mobile number or other details can be viewed, modified or deleted at any time by accessing your member area. Registered users who wish to close their account should read the instructions in our [help centre](http://support.productreview.com.au/), given the nature of our site it may be impossible to remove all your content and some residual information may remain on the site. 

##### Disclosing personal information

ProductReview does not sell or rent personal information to any third party. We may disclose your personal information to the police, government, or regulatory authorities, as required by law. 

Your profile and contributions on ProductReview will be publicly viewable and identifiable via your nickname and your chosen location (City). ProductReview will neither share your email address nor first and last names with other members, nor will we display them in any public manner, unless you expressly choose to have us do so. 

We may aggregate personal information from all of our users and provide that information in the aggregate to other parties, including advertisers, for marketing and promotional purposes. However, if we do so, that information will not be in a form that will allow any third party to identify you personally. 

##### Trans-border transfer of your personal information

ProductReview is an Australian entity however our servers, and some data we collect in the operation of this site, is currently hosted in the United States of America (USA). Any personal information you provide through your use of this Site will be transferred to our servers in the USA. By continuing to access and use this site, you consent to the application of Australian laws relating to the collection, use, and disclosure of your personal information and to the transfer of your personal information to the USA. 

##### Cookies

ProductReview uses cookies to remember who you are when you log-in, to tracking your browsing patterns and to customise your user experience on our site. The type of information we collect depends on what information and services you access and use, but generally do not contain or are not tied to your personal information. We may also use cookies for anonymous profiling purposes to tailor advertising to your preferences. If you do not wish to receive cookies, you can set your browser so that your computer does not accept them although this may prevent access to or limit some of the information and usability of our site. 

##### Security

We follow industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it (storage). However, no method of transmission over the Internet or via mobile device, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you become aware of unauthorised usage of your password, username or account you should contact us immediately. 

##### Links

Our website may contain links to other websites operated by third parties. We make no representations or warranties in relation to the privacy practices of any third party website and we are not responsible for the privacy policies or the content of any third party website. Third party websites are responsible for informing you about their own privacy practices.

##### Privacy Complaints

We take the protection of our customer's privacy very seriously. If you have any privacy concerns or believe that your personal information is inaccurate or has been collected, used or disclosed in a manner contrary to privacy law we encourage you to raise any concerns you have with us by emailing privacy@productreview.com.au so that we can take steps to address them. 

In most cases we will ask that you put your request in writing to us. We will investigate your complaint and will use reasonable endeavours to respond to you in writing within 30 days of receiving the written complaint. If we fail to respond to your complaint within 30 days of receiving it in writing or if you are dissatisfied with the response that you receive from us, you may have the right, depending on the jurisdiction, to make a complaint to the applicable regulator. 

##### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may change this privacy policy from time to time. Any updated versions of this privacy policy will be posted on our website. This privacy policy was last updated in May 2014.

##### More Information

More information on privacy is available at the website of the Office of the Australian Information Commissioner [www.oaic.gov.au](http://www.oaic.gov.au/).
